terawarner.com 2017-06-28

# Tera Warner - Detox Solutions for Home, Body & Heart

When you provide information through this website, we respect your privacy. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information. Your visit to this website is subject to this privacy policy.  

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you decide to complete a user registration form or survey, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, and telephone number), age group, gender, and areas of interest, and the products you use.

The information you provide may be used by us to create and deliver to you our newsletters, surveys or other communications containing product information, promotions or information concerning your order. If you prefer not to receive such communications, please see opt-out below.

We may use the information you provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as disclosed in this privacy policy.

We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular.

This website may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This privacy policy applies only to the information we collect on this website. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from our website or otherwise visit.

When you place an order via this website, all handling is provided by a secure third-party shopping cart. No financial data is ever stored on this website.

Opt-Out

When you sign up at this website, you may opt out of receiving future communications from us. You may unsubscribe by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any bulk e-mail you receive from us and following the instructions provided.
